So, what's your name?
それで、あなたの名前は何ですか？
What was your name?
あなたの名前は何でしたっけ？
I can't remember something so lame
そんなにつまらないことは思い出せない
'Cause I don't care
だって気にしないから
Yeah, I don't care
うん、気にしない
That a break up left you in despair
別れがあなたを絶望させたこと
Keep me off your track
私をあなたの道から遠ざけてください あなたと
I don't need you back
復縁する必要はありません
Crusades of guilt you put me through
あなたが私に課した罪悪感の十字軍
They make me sick
それらは私をうんざりさせます
To me, your life's irrelevant
私にとって、あなたの人生は無関係です
So, don't search for significance
だから、意義を探さないで
There's nothing about you I've missed
あなたについて私が見逃したことは何もありません
I forgot that you exist ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
私はあなたが存在することを忘れていました ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
So, what's it like?
それで、どんな感じですか？
What is it like?
それはどんな感じですか？
To leech on someone else the next night?
次の夜、別の誰かに寄生するためですか?
You know, it's fun
ねえ、楽しいことなの
It really is fun
本当に楽しい
To hear you blame me for crimes I've never done
ことなの やってもいない罪で君が僕を責めるのを聞くのは
Keep me off your track
僕を君の道から遠ざけておくんだ
I don't need you back
君に戻る必要はない
Crusades of guilt you put me through
君が僕に課した罪悪感の十字軍は
They make me sick
僕をうんざりさせる
To me, your life's irrelevant
僕にとって君の人生は無関係なんだ
So, don't search for significance
だから、意義を探さないで
There's nothing about you I've missed
君について見逃したことなんて何もない
I forgot that you exist
君が存在することを 忘れていた
¯\_(ツ)_/¯
Though, I've been thinking of maybe forgiving
でも、許すことも考えてたんだ 僕は
Am I crazy, am I strange?
狂ってるのかな、変なのかな？
You'll never change
あなたは決して変わらない
To me, your life's irrelevant
私にとって、あなたの人生は無関係だ
So, don't search for significance
だから、意義を探さないで
There's nothing about you I've missed
あなたについて私が見逃したことは何もない
I forgot that you exist
あなたが存在することを忘れていた
¯\_(ツ)_/¯
Guitars by @daniel_lee_music on instagram)
ギターはInstagramの@daniel_lee_musicによるもの)
Maybe, one day I'll get over this
いつかこのことを乗り越えられるかもしれない
But for now, you don't exist
でも今のところ、あなたは存在しない
No, to me you don't exist
いいえ、私にとってあなたは存在しない
I forgot that you exist ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
あなたが存在することを忘れていた ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
Subscribe to our patreon for early access to contents !
コンテンツに早期アクセスするには、パトレオンに登録してください！
Thanks for watching !
ご視聴ありがとうございました！